[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Diego] Listen to me. We don't
have to kill each other.
If we work together, we can get
Auntie Camia and Lily back.
We're going to turn the tables on them.
I'll give you what you want!
Diego!
[gunshot]
[Helena] Finally!
Helena, you monster!
Let me see my daughter before I die!
I won't let you kill my mother!
This is the end of the game. Game over!
No! Kill me, instead!
[Helena] Burn her! Burn that witch!
-[Arnaldo] I said, no!
-No!
Romulo! I said, stop it!
You, Helena, are not the only
player in this playground!
Remember, we are a family.
And we have to come up with the
final decision together as one.
[Diego] Now, bring Lily to me,
just as you promised!
You will never see Lily Cruz alive again.
[goon] Let's kill him
before he tries to escape.
[Magbanua] We need to wait
for our bosses' orders.
But keep an eye on him.
-I know you're watching me!
-[Julio] We'll drive her insane.
Just as she did my grandson.
And then we will be
laughing our heads off.
Because we Ardientes
always get the last laugh.
[Magbanua] Who disposed of Damian's body?
[goon] Ramirez and Salazar did.
[gunshots]
Where are Lily and Camia?
I don't know.
-Papa, what just happened?
-[Julio] I don't know!
[electricity buzzing]
Mom!
Lily, I'm here! Lily! Lily!
Where's my mother?!
[gunshots]
Lily!
You hear Lily?
Bring Lily out!
[tense music playing]
There!
[Lily shouting]
There's Lily!
[goon] Here she is!
Your daughter's here.
Go ahead and hug her!
[Camia sobbing]
[tense music playing]
Monsters! Monsters!
Go on.
Leave us.
[tense music playing]
-Lily Cruz!
-[gunshots]
[gunshots]
[groans]
[goon] You should thank the
Ardientes for keeping you alive.
You'd be dead if it were up to me.
[tense music continues playing]
Remember this?
I'm not done with you yet.
[tense music playing]
[gun cocks]
[goon] Don't!
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
[Camia cries]
This is all your fault!
-Mine?!
-[Helena] All our guards are down.
Even Romulo's dead!
If you're so brilliant,
what's your next move, huh?
Answer me! Answer me!
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[screams in frustration]
Do you really think you could escape?
[Camia grunts]
[Camia screaming]
Don't touch me, you bastard!
Get off of me!
[goon] I'm not done with you!
[tense music playing]
What are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do?!
-[Emilia] Ma.
-I think you should meditate.
Calm down.
Calm down?! This is all your fault!
Yes, you kidnapped Lily.
But you wanted to play games!
And now, we're about to lose.
You just wanna drag us all down!
Don't you raise your voice at Arnaldo!
That's right! Keep tolerating him!
-Of course! What do you want me to do?
-What?!
Want me to listen to Emilia,
instead? Is that it?
-Stop spoiling him!
-Yes! I'll do what I want!
Look what happened! Why?
Stop! Stop! Look! Look!
Lily Cruz has escaped!
What are we going to do now?
Papa, do something!
[tense music playing]
What now? Huh?
Are you enjoying the show, Ardientes?
Go ahead and have fun watching!
Because once I get out of here,
along with my mother,
I'll show you the meaning of fear!
[tense music playing]
Wait for me, Ardientes. I'm coming.
[brooding music playing]
[Julio] Watch! Watch, Lily Cruz!
Lily.
[suspenseful music building]
[groans]
[groaning]
[breathes heavily]
Lily. Lily!
What did you do to my daughter?
[wailing] Lily! Lily!
[glass breaking]
If you didn't stop me,
Lily Cruz would've bitten the dust by now!
I've run out of men and patience
because of that woman!
And she's coming here,
so we need to be careful.
You know how she is.
She might just walk on water
or grow wings.
-[Julio laughs]
-Like some kind of superhero.
Okay, by now, I'm so tired of saying this,
but please, calm down.
Look, you even broke Grandpa's
favorite vase.
She's alone, isn't she?
And, besides she has no idea where we are.
She doesn't even know where Camia is.
Before she can open the doors
to this house,
our men would've showered her
with bullets.
Don't be scared.
[whistles]
[Julio] Foul.
Ardiente men are born to rule.
I still have everything under
control, so please trust me.
No! This is my game!
And everybody plays by my rules!
[frustrated] Bullshit.
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
Are you going to talk?
[Magbanua scoffs]
Or should I just break your skull open?
[coughing]
Well?
You think you're so tough, huh?!
-[Damian fires shot]
-[screaming in pain]
[Magbanua laughs, groans]
[groans, laughs]
Even if you kill me,
you won't get anything from me.
[Magbanua laughs]
Stubborn, huh?
-Well, if that's it…
-[Magbanua sighs]
[gun cocks]
[phone buzzing]
-[Magbanua sighs]
-[phone buzzing]
[Damian] What's that?
[phone buzzing]
-[Damian] Let me check!
-Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
-[phone buzzing]
-[Magbanua groans]
[Magbanua breathing heavily]
What's this? What are you hiding here?
Did you exchange messages
with the Ardientes
about where Lily and Camia are?
Answer him!
I don't know.
-[Magbanua laughing]
-Nothing. Nothing? Nothing!
[grunts]
Are you sure you really
don't know anything?
Nothing at all?
Hold on! Hold on! Give me his phone.
[Magbanua breathing heavily]
Hold still.
[Magbanua] No. No.
[Magbanua groans]
[Magbanua] No!
[Magbanua screaming]
[Magbanua breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
GO TO THE WAREHOUSE IN SITIO OTSO
AND MAKE SURE THAT WOMAN
DOESN'T GET OUT.
I don't think they're together.
Only one address is mentioned here.
Where is the other one?
Answer me!
[Magbanua] I was only ordered
to keep watch on you.
I have no idea where Lily and Camia are.
[laughs]
[tense music playing]
[Diego] Let's go.
[Magbanua laughing]
[screaming in pain]
[groans]
[Magbanua laughing]
[tense music playing]
I need to be one step ahead
of the Ardientes.
I don't have time to find an easy way out.
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
Something's wrong, Jepoy.
Arnaldo hasn't answered any of my calls.
[phone ringing]
Excuse me. Oh, the idiots are calling.
Anna?
Arnaldo.
Jepoy and I can't keep waiting.
With every minute,
Auntie Camia's and Lily's lives
are in even more danger.
Have you heard anything
about where they are?
Give me that.
Where's Lily and Auntie Camia?
Anna, Jepoy, I think I know where Lily is.
[brooding music playing]
Thanks, Arnaldo.
I'll text you her location, but don't tell
anyone else, okay?
Don't bring anyone either.
He said not to bring anyone else.
He said that?
And why did you do that?
Did you hit your head again?
Are you trying to get caught?
You're so mean. Please, I'm bored.
I wanna be in this game too, like her.
And if for some cosmic reason,
they came up with a
plan to ruin our plan,
at least I could tell you
in advance, right?
It's like hitting two birds--
Oh, no. Three birds with one stone.
You are staying here.
What if something happens to you?
Grandpa.
Emilia, let your son play with his toys.
Besides, don't you want this?
Now, we'll finally have eyes
where our cameras can't see.
And besides, just in case
Lily Cruz is there…
I know exactly what to do.
[sinister music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[music continues]
[sinister music playing]
[beeps]
[line ringing]
Emilia.
Oh, come on, Jaguar.
You always call at the worst times.
[Emilia] Listen, I can't stay
on the line that long.
Because, as of now,
we're having a very big
family emergency meeting.
Why did you call?
I just wanted to check…
if you were all right.
I was just thinking
about your bullet wound.
Has it healed yet?
That's really sweet of you,
but you have to remember
that I'm a big girl already.
I can take care of myself.
Well, Emilia, that's exactly
what I want to do.
I want to help you, take care of you.
And, more than anything, to support you
with everything you're going through.
If you will let me, that is.
Okay, let's meet up.
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
[Jepoy] Yeah, I'm here.
[ominous music building]
Anna, don't be stubborn.
This place is dangerous.
Yeah, I'll be careful.
We'll talk when I get back, okay?
Bye.
[ominous music playing]
[tense music playing]
Hey.
Don't shoot, Jepoy. It's me.
Why do you have a gun, Arnaldo?
Where did you get that?
I found it upstairs.
Is he still alive?
Yeah.
Can I keep this?
Wait, where is Anna?
I won't take Anna here.
It's too dangerous.
Where is Lily?
[stutters] I don't know
what happened, either.
All I know is they were brought here.
We better look for them. They
should be around here somewhere.
Come on!
[tense music playing]
[melancholic music playing]
[Camia] You monsters!
What are you going to do to me?
Mom!
[tense music playing]
God, please lead me to where my mother is.
Mom, I'll protect you
until my last breath.
I'll save you from Helena
and the Ardientes.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia] Oh my God, Jaguar.
You'd better be here and show up
because I had to sneak out
just to see you.
[tense music playing]
Raul?
What are you doing here?
What about you,
what are you doing here, huh?
Are you here to meet with your accomplice?
Where is Diego?
It's none of your business.
You followed me here, didn't you?
I didn't follow you. Where's Diego?
Where's my son? Where is he?
Let go of me, Raul! Let go of me!
-Bring out my son.
-Let go of me.
Why, Emilia? Are you going to kill me?
Can you do it?
Emilia, you've threatened me
countless times.
But I'm still alive.
You want to know why?
You can't kill me because you love me.
And that's your weakness.
After everything, Raul?
After everything we've been through,
you'll still choose
your bastard son over me?
I keep giving you chances, Raul,
but time and time again,
you keep showing me
you don't deserve to live!
You were the ones who
brought Lily and Camia Cruz
into our lives!
Those people keep making
my family's life miserable.
They keep making my life miserable!
It's all your fault, Raul!
It's all your fault!
Fine.
It's my fault, I admit it.
But I paid for it a long time ago.
I've more than made up for it.
When my son and I moved into your house,
my life became a living hell.
But I put up with all of you.
You know why?
Because I wanted to be powerful like you.
The Ardientes. Because I knew I would need
to protect my son someday
from monsters like you!
I will kill you, Raul!
I will kill you and your son!
You don't need to kill me anymore.
Because I've been mourning my death
from the day we got married, Emilia.
[somber music playing]
I turned into a monster because
of my love for you, Raul.
Well, sorry. You married me, remember?
I never loved you.
Even then, I knew
you weren't worthy of my love.
Don't you dare come near me, Raul.
Don't you dare come near me
because you and your son
are about to meet again in hell.
Don't you dare follow me, Raul.
[Damian groaning]
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
There aren't a lot of guards.
I'm going in.
I'm coming with you.
You sure you can do it?
You're hurt pretty bad.
I can do it.
Use this.
[phone buzzing]
Hello, Dad?
Diego? Diego, where are you?
The Ardientes have Lily and Auntie Camia.
I'm with Mister Damian.
We're going to rescue them.
Son, it's too dangerous.
They will kill you.
We need to meet so I can help you.
I'll send you the location.
We'll meet you here.
Okay. Be careful.
[tense music playing]
Damn you, Raul.
I will make sure your bastard son dies!
Damn you!
[sobbing]
-Diego.
-Dad.
Raul, are you sure you're ready
to go against the Ardientes?
For my son.
I'm willing to do it for my son.
[tense music playing]
Now you're the true, one and only Jaguar.
I worked for Red Dragon once,
but I turned my back
on that life a long time ago.
Mister Damian, thank you
for helping me fight
Red Dragon's minions.
Thank you for rescuing my son.
I don't deserve your gratitude
because I've hurt Camia and Lily
so many times.
We should just work together to find them.
Use that mask to right what's wrong.
[ominous music playing]
[action music playing]
I'll call you two once I find them.
Dad, please be careful.
Damian.
[action music playing]
Emilia, is everything okay?
[Julio] Emilia, what's wrong with you?
Why did you leave without telling us?
I'm okay, Mama.
Sorry, I just had to fix something.
[tense music playing]
Clear. The entrance is clear.
What the hell is Jaguar doing there?
You two aren't good with cats, are you?
Looks like you both
got clawed in the face.
[tense music playing]
-[goon] Hey!
-[gunshots]
The intruder's here!
[tense music playing]
What?!
[gunshots]
[goon] What was that?
-Gunshots?
-Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
[action music playing]
What's this?
That's impossible. Damian is dead.
I saw Diego kill Damian myself.
Dad.
You two go upstairs. I'll search here.
[tense music playing]
Keep an eye on her.
[goon] Yes, Boss. I got this.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia sighs]
Of all the blasted--
How many lives does
that damn Cruz family have?!
From the mother to the uncle
and down to the daughter,
it's like they've all got nine lives!
I won't let those lowlifes outsmart us.
We are the predators and not them!
Oh, yeah. Look what's happening.
[action music playing]
[Damian] Diego, check upstairs.
I'll look here. Go.
[action music playing]
Lily? Auntie Camia?
[tense music playing]
[Damian] Camia!
[sinister music playing]
Lily!
-Lily!
-Hey, shut up!
Lily!
[tense music playing]
[goon grunting]
Damian?
Damn you, Jaguar!
I'm going to kill you.
I'll kill you!
-Emilia? Emilia!
-Emilia!
Emilia!
[tense music playing]
[chains rattling]
Damian, I'm so glad you're here.
[suspenseful music playing]
Camia, please let me make it up to you.
Wait, there are two Jaguars?
It doesn't matter
how many Jaguars there are.
What matters now is your safety. Come on.
What about my daughter?
We have to save Lily.
I'm with Damian and Diego.
They're looking for her.
Let's go, Camia.
I said take your hands off me!
Sir! Don't touch me!
Sir! Let me go! Let me go!
You'll all pay for this!
Locking me up all those years
wasn't "saving" me.
You're the root of all
my family's misfortunes!
You robbed me of my life!
Raul, why are you doing this?
Camia, let me make up
for everything I've done.
Let's go. We don't have much time.
[tense music playing]
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Drop it! Put it down.
Lily, Auntie Camia.
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
-Camia.
-Damian.
Thank goodness you're safe.
Where's Lily? Where's my daughter?
Diego and I searched the whole place,
but if you're the only one here,
then that means
they hid Lily somewhere else.
Damian, we have to find Lily.
The Ardientes are going to kill her.
We have to hurry. Time's running out.
Let's go out the back.
[goon] Hurry up! The prisoner has escaped!
This way. This way.
The prisoner has escaped! Did you see her?
[goon 2] She's not at the back.
You two, search the back again!
You two, come with me!
[tense music playing]
They're heading out back.
Let's go through the front.
Come on. Let's go, come on.
[tense music playing]
[cocks gun] What happened?
We heard gunshots inside, Madam.
And you're out here standing?!
Out of my way!
What? You let them get away too?
You're such an idiot! Come on, let's go!
Sorry, boss.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia] What happened here?
Idiots, every single one of you!
You two, stand guard here!
Got it? You're all so stupid!
I'm sure they haven't
gotten away yet, ma'am.
Shut up!
So, Helena, are you ready to watch
Emilia make a fool
out of herself for the nth time?
You know, she's always been a failure.
But I'm used to it by now.
[tense music playing]
The only good thing is that
I am always ready.
So, if anything goes wrong,
I have a plan B,
I have a plan C, and I have got plans up
to the letter Z just to get the job done.
What do you think you're doing?
Doing what you women can't -- my best.
Helena, give me back my phone.
Come and get me if you can, Julio.
No, give me back my phone.
Oops! My bad.
Who's in control now, huh, Julio?
[scoffs] Like I told you.
My game, my rules!
I'm telling you, Helena.
If there's one thing that's
dangerous in this world…
it's a humiliated man!
[Julio groans]
You're wrong, Julio.
There is something more
dangerous than a humiliated man!
It's a vengeful woman!
[Helena shouting]
[laughing]
[sinister music playing]
[tense music playing]
Damian, where's Diego?
Where is he?
I'll be the one to look for him.
Damian, you take care of Camia.
I'm out of bullets.
But I'll manage. Now, go.
[Raul grunts]
I'm out of bullets too.
Come on, let's go.
[Emilia shouting] You're all so stupid!
[Damian mumbling quietly]
[unsettling music]
[Damian grunts]
What happened?
How the hell did they get away?
Someone helped the prisoner escape, ma'am.
Go back and get reinforcements!
And make it quick!
You're all so stupid!
And what are you doing there?
Search the whole area! You useless idiots!
Why are you still standing there?
Camia?
Damian?
Yoo-hoo. Where are you two?
Now, don't test me.
I'm getting impatient!
[Emilia shouting] Camia!
[phone ringing]
Yes, Mama?
Emilia, go to your right.
Your right, behind the crates.
[suspenseful music playing]
Camia Cruz is there
with the two prodigal Jaguars.
Go get them.
Thanks, Mama. You're the best.
[laughing]
Of all the places to hide.
Come on out of there!
Camia, Damian, out!
My patience is wearing thin.
I don't like waiting!
One!
[gunshot]
-Two!
-[gunshot]
-Three!
-[Raul grunts]
Let go, Jaguar!
[Emilia struggling]
You traitor!
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[Jaguar breathing heavily]
[somber music playing]
-[Raul groans]
-I'm going to kill you!
Emilia…
[Raul groans, coughs]
[dramatic music playing]
[Raul groans]
[sobbing]
[dramatic music playing]
[screaming]
[Emilia screaming] Raul!
[Emilia wailing]
[tense music playing]
[sobbing] Raul!
Arnaldo, I've searched the whole place,
but they aren't here.
Do you think I'm stupid? Where are they?
Please forgive me for failing
to give you a good life, son.
You killed everyone I love!
What a surprise to see you, Lily Cruz!
-[gunshot]
-[Emilia] Before this night is over,
I'll have my revenge on you
and your daughter!
No matter how many times
you try to bury us,
we'll always come back to haunt you!
I can't wait to kill all you Ardientes!
Did I stress you out?
[Lily] Emilia!
If you kill my mother, I'll kill yours!
[theme music playing]